Krunal Jethva

A Computer Engineering student from VVP Engineering College, Rajkot, Gujarat, India. Worked on many competitive platforms and projects using **Python, C#, TypeScript** as the primary language and databases like **MySQL, MongoDB**.

Rajkot,, Gujarat, india +91 9924253527 krunaljethva90@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/krunal-jethva/ krunal-ctrl.github.io/ github.com/krunal-ctrl

EXPERIENCE

Tark Technologies, Rajkot—SDE Intern

Sep 2021 - Jul 2022 (Angular, .NET, TSQL)

Here I had been working on an airline project which includes .NET web API, Angular as a technology stack. Learning Software practices, Software architecture.

Working on a live project (POS for a restaurant) for the past month as part of the onboarding process as junior software engineer.

Tark Technologies, Rajkot—Jr. Software Engineer

Jul 2022 - PRESENT (Angular, .NET, TSQL)

Working on a client project (POS for a restaurant) in which i am responsible for develop, test and deploy various tasks

PROJECTS (College)

Transformer Conversation Chat

Python (Flask, textblob), SQL, JavaScript, HTML

Its NLP base chat app that translates the message received from the other side in the receiver's native language. It also includes Login, signup activity.

RMC Chatbot

Python (RASA framework), YML

a chatbot that will make user's interaction with RMC's website smooth and the whole experience fun. Chatbot will be able to respond to all user queries regarding any service provided by RMC

EDUCATION

V.V.P. Engineering College, Rajkot —Computer Engg.

AUg 2018 - present

Alpha High School, Junagadh — Sci(PCM)

JUNE 2016 - MARCH 2018

SKILLS

Programming Languages: C#,JavaScript, TypeScript, Python, JAVA, C,

Other: Docker, GCP, AWS

Good communication skill and good team player

Exploring web developing, data-science fields.

ACCOMPLISHMENTS

Awarded Best **Programmers** many times during 2018, 2019, 2020.

Secured **3rd rank** in zone level **coding competition**.

Member of **Student Developer Club (DSC)** in college

Earned many **certificates** from popular websites like **coursera**, **datacamp**, **GCP**.

OTHER

Actively participating in coding completion on various platforms